Marcin Kostrzemski

Full-stack developer ⊕ Toruń, Poland, CET











About

Full-stack developer with a focused background in web development for over 2 years and a total of 5 years in the IT field. Proficient in Vue, Laravel, MySQL and related technologies, I actively engage in side projects to continuously enhance my skills. Programming is not just a profession but a hobby for me. I see myself as versatile, always eager to learn and adapt to new technologies. Recently I've been deep diving into React, Typescript, Next.js and Three.js.

Work Experience

Appworks Software House

2021 - now

Full-stack developer

During my time at Appworks, I managed to gain valuable experience, and deepen my knowledge related to web development. Over a span of more than two years, I actively participated in numerous projects, often as the lead developer. Most of them are mentioned in the "Projects" section.

Gmodstore Freelance

Remote

2017 - now

Developer / Content creator

I successfully developed and sold paid modifications for the popular game Garry's Mod, enhancing my proficiency in complex programming and gaining a solid understanding of the basics of 3D graphics. I created solutions that continue to be utilized by numerous server owners, demonstrating their ongoing value. Despite the niche nature of this endeavor, I managed to raise over \$20,000, showcasing the impact of my work on the gaming community.

Education

Nicolaus Copernicus University in Toruń

2019 - 2022

Engineering degree in information technology

Skills

JavaScript

TypeScript

Vue

React

PHP/Laravel

Next.js

Three.js

JQuery

Projects

PlanetGen3D •

A 3D universe builder app. It focuses on creating planet and star constellations while allowing customization.

Side Project React TypeScript Next.js

Three.js + Fiber

Harasówka ERP

A larger scale ERP web app tailored for a local inn, comprising various modules including a knowledge base, warehouse management, work time tracking, an administrator suite, and more.

Lead Developer Vue PHP/Laravel MySQL

Promotion System

A highly scalable web app module designed for employee promotions. The system operates across multiple companies and their databases.

Lead Developer Vue PHP/Laravel MySQL

WhatsApp Mass Sender •

The application utilizes the Blueticks API to efficiently send scheduled messages to selected recipients in bulk.

Lead Developer Vue PHP/Laravel MySQL

Togo.to Rewrite

I was assigned a task of completely rewriting Togo.to website from JQuery & Blade templates to Vue & Inertia.

Vue PHP/Laravel MySQL

PortfolioNext •

My personal portfolio. From my latest projects to a glimpse of my professional journey, it's an overview of my capabilities and personality.

Side Project React TypeScript Next.js

Three.js + Fiber

KPE Calculator

ERP web app designed to assist solar panel sales proffesionals in their work.

Lead Developer Vue PHP/Laravel MySQL

Supply Demand System

Web app module designed to manage supply requests.

Lead Developer Vue PHP/Laravel MySQL

Sportigio •

I actively contribute to the development of the Sportigio platform, handling both frontend and back-end tasks.

JQuery PHP/Laravel MySQL

Gmod modifications •

Game scripts altering various aspects of the game, with a dominant focus on enhancing roleplay gamemodes.

Freelance Lua 3D